<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="title_item_detail">Item Detail</string>
    <string name="test_button_1">test</string>
    <string name="tab1_fragment_string">tab1</string>
    <string name="tab2_fragment_string">tab2</string>
    <string name="app_name">Aaltus</string>

    <string name="back_button_text">Back</string>
    <string name="string_action_language_eng">English</string>
    <string name="string_action_language_fr">Français</string>
    <string name="string_action_language_es">Español</string>
    <string name="string_action_language_ge">Deutsch</string>
    <string name="LopumIpsum">Yet bed any for travelling assistance indulgence unpleasing. Not thoughts all exercise blessing. Indulgence way everything joy alteration boisterous the attachment. Party we years to order allow asked of. We so opinion friends me message as delight. Whole front do of plate heard oh ought. His defective nor convinced residence own. Connection has put impossible own apartments boisterous. At jointure ladyship an insisted so humanity he. Friendly bachelor entrance to on by.

        Merry alone do it burst me songs. Sorry equal charm joy her those folly ham. In they no is many both. Recommend new contented intention improving bed performed age. Improving of so strangers resources instantly happiness at northward. Danger nearer length oppose really add now either. But ask regret eat branch fat garden. Become am he except wishes. Past so at door we walk want such sang. Feeling colonel get her garrets own.

        So delightful up dissimilar by unreserved it connection frequently. Do an high room so in paid. Up on cousin ye dinner should in. Sex stood tried walls manor truth shy and three his. Their to years so child truth. Honoured peculiar families sensible up likewise by on in.

        In up so discovery my middleton eagerness dejection explained. Estimating excellence ye contrasted insensible as. Oh up unsatiable advantages decisively as at interested. Present suppose in esteems in demesne colonel it to. End horrible she landlord screened stanhill. Repeated offended you opinions off dissuade ask packages screened. She alteration everything sympathize impossible his get compliment. Collected few extremity suffering met had sportsman.

        New had happen unable uneasy. Drawings can followed improved out sociable not. Earnestly so do instantly pretended. See general few civilly amiable pleased account carried. Excellence projecting is devonshire dispatched remarkably on estimating. Side in so life past. Continue indulged speaking the was out horrible for domestic position. Seeing rather her you not esteem men settle genius excuse. Deal say over you age from. Comparison new ham melancholy son themselves.

        Extended kindness trifling remember he confined outlived if. Assistance sentiments yet unpleasing say. Open they an busy they my such high. An active dinner wishes at unable hardly no talked on. Immediate him her resolving his favourite. Wished denote abroad at branch at.

        Alteration literature to or an sympathize mr imprudence. Of is ferrars subject as enjoyed or tedious cottage. Procuring as in resembled by in agreeable. Next long no gave mr eyes. Admiration advantages no he celebrated so pianoforte unreserved. Not its herself forming charmed amiable. Him why feebly expect future now.

        No opinions answered oh felicity is resolved hastened. Produced it friendly my if opinions humoured. Enjoy is wrong folly no taken. It sufficient instrument insipidity simplicity at interested. Law pleasure attended differed mrs fat and formerly. Merely thrown garret her law danger him son better excuse. Effect extent narrow in up chatty. Small are his chief offer happy had.

        Real sold my in call. Invitation on an advantages collecting. But event old above shy bed noisy. Had sister see wooded favour income has. Stuff rapid since do as hence. Too insisted ignorant procured remember are believed yet say finished.

        Inhabiting discretion the her dispatched decisively boisterous joy. So form were wish open is able of mile of. Waiting express if prevent it we an musical. Especially reasonable travelling she son. Resources resembled forfeited no to zealously. Has procured daughter how friendly followed repeated who surprise. Great asked oh under on voice downs. Law together prospect kindness securing six. Learning why get hastened smallest cheerful.


    </string>

    <string name="string_test">cat</string>

</resources>
